Guide to the Arthur Cort Holden papers, 1920-1987
Holden, Arthur Cort papers, 1920-1987
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Arthur Cort Holden papers, 1920-1987
3748
Arthur Cort Holden, 1890-
110.1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, blueprints, financial records, photographs, articles, surveys, reports, drafts and copies of articles and books, and bound volumes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection includes extensive correspondence, blueprints, sketches, drawings, financial records, and photographs from Holden's private practice around New York City; correspondence, articles, surveys and reports documenting his service on many boards, committees, and commissions. Also included are drafts and copies of articles and books including The Settlement Idea and Sonnets for My City; and a bound volume, "Are Bankers Credit Allocators?", of photocopies of a collection of commentaries, based on a New York Times article.
BIOGRAPHICAL DATA
Firms:
Arthur C. Holden & Associates, 1920-1930, Principal
Holden, McLaughlin & Associates, 1930-1953, Partner
Holden, Egan & Associates, 1953-1960
Holden, Egan, Wilson & Corser, 1960-1967
Holden, Yang, Raemsch & Corser, 1967-
Principal works:
Madison Square Boys Club, New York City, 1924
Sussex Garden Apartments, Rye, New York, 1942
General Charles Berry Houses, New York, 1951
Guggenheim Museum with Frank Lloyd Wright, 1959
Queensborough Community College, with F.P. Wiedersum, 1968
Awards:
Chairman, Conference on Planning Man's Environment, Princeton University Bi-Centennial, 1946-1947
Medal of Honor, New York Chapter, American Institute of Architects, 1957
Education:
Litt.B., Princeton (hons.), 1912
B.Arch. & Am.Econ., Columbia Univ., 1915
Lambda Alpha, 1967
Lectured: Housing, Princeton, Mass. Institute of Tech., Pa. State Univ., Vassar, Bennington
Public service:
President and Chairman of the Board of New York Urban League, Inc. 1922-1931
President's Commission on Home Building and Home Ownership, 1928-1930
National Construction Council, 1931-1932
Mayor LaGuardia's Committee on City Planning, 1934-1938
Trustee, Lenox Hill Hospital, New York City, 1951-1960
Government service:
New York National Guard, chief plant secretary, hull division, drafting room, U.S. Navy Yard, Brooklyn, 1917-1919
Publications:
Author and illustrator: Brick Architecture of the Colonial Period in Maryland and Virginia, 1919
Author: The Settlement Idea: A Vision of Social Justice, 1922
Author and illustrator: Money and Motion: The Social Function of Banking, 1940
Author and illustrator: Sonnets for My City: An Essay on the Kinship of Art and Finance, 1965
Author: Can We Deal Intelligently with Inflation?, n.d.
American Institute of Architects, New York Chapter:
Chairman of civic design, 1935-1942
Member of Executive Committee, 1943-1947
Chairman of Housing Committee, 1947-1949
Director, New York Region, 1949-1952
Vice Chairman, Committee on Post-War Planning, 1944-1946
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes extensive correspondence, blueprints, sketches, drawings, financial records, and photographs from Holden's private practice around New York City; correspondence, articles, surveys and reports documenting his service on many boards, committees, and commissions including the Executive (1943-1947), Civic Design (1935-1942), and Housing (1947-1949) Committees of the New York Chapter of the American Institute of Architects, the New York Urban League, Inc. (1922-1923), the A.I.A. Committee on Post-war Planning (1944-1946), the President's Commission on Home Building and Home Ownership (1928-1930), the National Construction Council (1931-1932), and the Mayor's Committee on City Planning, New York City (1934-1938); and personal correspondence (1920-1953). Also included are drafts and copies of articles and books including The Settlement Idea and Sonnets for My City; and a bound volume, "Are Bankers Credit Allocators?", of photocopies of a collection of commentaries, based on a New York Times article.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Holden, Arthur Cort, 1890-; Holden, Arthur Cort, 1890- Settlement idea.; Holden, Arthur Cort, 1890- Sonnets for my city.; American Institute of Architects. New York Chapter. Executive Committee.; American Institute of Architects. New York Chapter. Civic Design Committee.; American Institute of Architects. New York Chapter. Housing Committee.; American Institute of Architects. Committee on Post-war Planning.; New York Urban League.; President's Commission on Home Building and Home Ownership.; National Construction Council.; New York (N.Y.). Committee on City Planning.; Lambda Alpha International. New York Chapter.
Subjects:
Housing.; City planning--New York (State).; City planning.; Urban design.; Architects.; City planners.
Places:
New York (N.Y.)--City planning.
Form and Genre Terms:
Blueprints.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Office files, 1921-1937, firms of Arthur C. Holden & Associates, 1920-1930 and Holden, McLaughlin & Associates, 1930-1953
Boxes 1-8
Series II. Office files, 1935-1942, firm of Holden, McLaughlin & Associates, 1930-1953
Boxes 9-20
Series III. Miriam Holden, personal
Box 19
Series IV. Blueprints
Boxes 21-51, 98
Series V. A.C.H., personal, 1920-1942
Boxes 52-56
Series VI. Housing, 1930-1942
Boxes 57-66
Series VII. Housing, 1939-1945
Boxes 67-72
Series VIII. Miscellaneous
Boxes 73-104
Series IX. Oversized photos and drawings from the Architectural League of New York Annual Exhibitions
Series X. Maps
Series XI. Rolled plans
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Office Files, 1921-1937, firms of Arthur C. Holden & Associates, 1920-1930 and Holden, McLaughlin & Associates, 1930-1953
  Boxes 1-5 may have originally consisted of a separate series for Housing, Leonard Cox and John T. Boyd, Jr., papers. However, it was impossible to reconstruct those series. Wherever possible the original heading is indicated on the folder, and it is filed under that heading, except for place names which are alphabetically filed. The office files include correspondence, articles, book drafts, published material and notes.
  Financial records (Boxes 5-7) contain income tax information, bills rendered and paid, certificates rendered and paid, cost sheets and unidentified material.
  - A-C (Box 1)
  - D-Mc (Box 2)
  - Mi-Po (Box 3)
  - Pr-W (Box 4)
  - Unidentified material and financial records including income tax papers (Box 5)
  - Financial records including bills rendered and paid, certificates rendered and paid (Box 6)
  - Cost sheets, 1930-1931, and n.d. (Box 7)
  - S,U (Box 8)
- Series II. Office Files, 1935-1942, Firm of Holden, McLaughlin and Associates, 1930-1953
  Some items from the 1921-1937 office files including administration, 1926-1930, were carried over into this series. Here financial records such as bills rendered are interfiled with the correspondence which forms the bulk of the series. Some printed material.
  - A-Bo (Box 9)
  - Bu-D (Box 10)
  - E-Ho (Box 11)
  - Ho-Ma (Box 12)
  - Ma-Me, including Madison Square Boys Club (Box 13)
  - Me-Mz (Box 14)
  - N-Q (Box 15)
  - R-San (Box 16)
  - San-T, including Sussex Garden Apartments (Box 17)
  - U-Wi (Box 18)
  - Wi-Z, Time Record Sheets (Box 19)
  - Princeton Bi-Centennial, 1946-1947, A.C.H. personal, 1946-1949 (Box 20)
- Series III. Miriam Holden, personal
  - Correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 19)
- Series IV. Blueprints
  - A-Az, including All Soul's, School of the Annunciation (Box 21)
  - Ba-Bh, including General Charles W. Berry Apartment Houses (Box 22)
  - Bi-Bre, including Biblical Seminary, Boys Brotherhood Republic (Box 23)
  - Bri-Ci, including Brookdale Reformed Church (Box 24)
  - C-Dar (Box 25)
  - Dar-E (Box 26)
  - F-Fo, including Firehouses #91, 93, 95 and Fincke (Box 27)
  - Fr-Go, Ben Franklin (Box 28)
  - Go-Gz, including Goodwill Apartments, Grolier Club (Box 29)
  - H-Hi, including Heightstown (Box 30)
  - Hi-In, including Heightstown (continued) and Independence Houses (Box 31)
  - It-La, including Katonah (Box 32)
  - Le-Ma, including Little Church, Lower East Side (Box 33)
  - Mogadiscio U.S. Embassy (Box 34)
  - H, M, misc. (Box 98)
  - Mog-Nev (Box 35)
  - New B.-New York Hospital, including N.Y. Hospital, West Division, New Delaware, New Castle, Delaware Town Hall (Box 36)
  - N.Y.I.T.-Norwalk, including N.Y.I.T. (Box 37)
  - Nor-Par, including Parkview Supermarket (Box 38)
  - Par-Pla (Box 39)
  - Pla-Rre (Box 40)
  - Pre-Pz (Box 41)
  - Q-Rad (Box 42)
  - Rat-Rz (Box 43)
  - S-Sta (Box 44)
  - Sto-Stt (Box 45)
  - Stt-Sw (Box 46)
  - Misc. S, R, including Rosedale Elementary School (Box 47)
  - Ta-Tu, including Turin house (Box 48)
  - Tu-Tz, U (1 item)-Wat, including addl. Turin House (Box 49)
  - Wat-Wil (Box 50)
  - Woo-Z (Box 51)
- Series V. A.C.H. personal, 1920-1942
  Contains personal and non-office-related business correspondence, memorandums, and some published material including papers related to the Emergency Relief Association, Inc. (Holden was a Director), 1932-1933; the N.Y. Urban League; the N.Y. Society of Architects; Princeton University; Quogue, N.Y. organizations; the Madison Square Boys Club Committee of Management; insurance, income tax, family members, finance, and the Holdens' home.
  - A-E (Box 52)
  - F-Ho (Box 53)
  - Ho-M (Box 54)
  - N-Q (Box 55)
  - R-Z, The Real Estate Board of N.Y. Diary and Manual, 1941; four checkbooks for Apr. 1941-May 1942; Brooklyn Garden Apartments Reports for Feb., May, Aug., Nov., 1941 and 1942. (Box 56)
- Series VI. Housing 1930-1942
  Includes correspondence related to housing and organizations interested in housing including the N.Y. Chapter of American Institute of Architects, Committee on Urban Land Use, Committee on Building, Housing Committee, Committee on Multiple Unit Housing, Civic Design Committee; the American Institute of Architects Committee on Industrial Relations, Committee on Professional Practice, Committee on Meetings and Public Information, the Architects Emergency Committee, the Architectural League of N.Y., the National Construction Council, and the Citizen's Housing Council.
  - A-A.I.A., New York Chapter (Box 57)
  - A.I.A., New York-Ci (Box 58)
  - Ci-Committee on Special Lectures (Box 59)
  - Con-Hol (Box 60)
  - Let-Mer (Box 61)
  - Let-Mer (continued) (Box 62)
  - Mer-Nat (Box 63)
  - Nat-New York City (Box 64)
  - New York Chapter-Rh (Box 65)
  - Ri-U (Box 66)
- Series VII. Housing 1939-1945
  Includes correspondence related to housing and housing organizations including Snag Club, the Real Estate Board of New York, the New York Society of Architects, the New York Building Congress, and the American Institute of Architects, Post-war Construction Committee.
  - A, Bu, including A.I.A. Post-war Construction Committee (Box 67)
  - C-Hi (Box 68)
  - I-Mz (Box 69)
  - N-New York Building Congress (Box 70)
  - New York Urban-Reg. (Box 71)
  - S-Z (Box 72)
- Series VIII. Miscellaneous
  - Newspapers and clippings, court transcript (Box 73)
  - Contract forms issued by A.I.A. and misc. (Box 74)
  - J.W.W. Thompson material (Box 75)
  - A.I.A. and misc. (Box 76)
  - A.I.A. (continued - 4 items) and photographs (Box 77)
  - Photographs (Box 78)
  - Kodak prints, report on Minetta Place Apartments, 1926, and A.C.H. personal, 1939, 1944-46 (Box 79)
  - Office and personal, 1945-1950 (Box 80)
  - Office, 1945-1950, continued, and A.C.H. personal, 1939-1946, A-G (Box 81)
  - A.C.H. personal, 1939-1946, H-R (Box 82)
  - A.C.H. personal, S-Z, 1939-1946, checkbooks, 1939, estate of Alice Holden, 1937-1939, unidentified publications, newspapers, stock ledger (Box 83)
  - G-P personal, 1941-1953 (Box 84)
  - Office, 1945-1950 (Box 85)
  - Misc., (including Real Estate Board publications) H-O (Box 86)
  - Community Planning, some A.C.H. personal, U,V,W (Box 87)
  - Community Planning, some A.C.H. personal, W, Administration, 1931-1933, literary, (drafts of articles and correspondence with publishers), 1932-1943 (Box 88)
  - Literary, continued, Egan and Holden files, A-F, 1956-1967 (Box 89)
  - Egan and Holden, G-Z, photos of A.C.H., 1956-1967 (Box 90)
  - Writings on housing, planning, and civic design, speeches and contributions to periodicals (Box 91)
  - Writings continued, correspondence to 1939 J.W.W. Thompson (Box 92)
  - Correspondence to 1939, A-H (Box 93)
  - Correspondence to 1939, I-W (Box 94)
  - Correspondence to 1939, W-Z, specifications (Box 95)
  - Literary and building codes, L-V (Box 96)
  - Literary and building codes, W-Z (Box 97)
  - Zoning, A-F, 1946-1954 historical and esthetic (Box 99)
  - Zoning, historical and esthetic, continued (Box 100)
  - Books
    - The Settlement Idea: A Vision of Social Justice Arthur C. Holden, N.Y.: The Macmillan Co., 1922 (Box 9)
    - Sonnets for My City: An Essay on the Kinship of Art and Finance N.Y.: Schulte Publishing Co., 1965 (Box 9)
    - Credit Extending vs. Money Lending 1976 (Box 9)
    - Is It Bankruptcy? 1976 Part 3 (Box 9)
    - Studies on the Financial Plight of N.Y. (Box 9)
  - Misc. sketches and drawings (Box 101)
  - Progress and Prosperity: A Suggested Program by Adelbert Ames, Jr. Photocopy of transcript (Box 102)
  - Appendix E: The Seventh Great Step in Finance? by A.C.H Photocopy of transcript (Box 102)
  - Are Bankers Credit Allocators? Comments Collected by A.C.Holden Bound photocopies of letters (Box 102)
  - Land Usage: Housing and Planning 1936 Land Utilization Committee of the New York Building Congress, ed. A.C.H. and Oscar Fisher (Box 102)
  - Correspondence, A-W, and misc.
    - For a Better City Pamphlet by A.C.H. (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - "A" Miscellaneous - 1950s and 1960s (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - "A" Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - AFL-CIO (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - AIA-Presidents (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Anshen, R.N. (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - "B" (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Boney, Leslie (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Botsai, Elmer (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - "C" Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Caldiero, Frank (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Clay, George Roberts II 1953-1977 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Family Correspondence (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Federal Reserve Bank (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - "H" Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Huzar, Mary (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - "J" Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Jaffee, Professor Dwight M. (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Kahn, Ernest (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Kaim, Julius R. Kaim (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Lewis, George, and "L" Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - "M" Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Princeton, Class of '12 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - "W" Miscellaneous (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Watson, Jack B. (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - Weinberg, Robert C. (FAIA) (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - Houston & Peoria Studies (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Survey (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Maps (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Maintenance cost tables [photostats] (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Harlem Income & Rehl Study 1935 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Hilda Smith, topographical map (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence and Writings
    - Personal: Army Discharge, photograph 1917 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Corresp. with McGovern, Grove, Yeomans (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Class of '12 Birthday Cards (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Essays and Sermons (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Dartmouth Eye Institute (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - "Vietnam - U.S. Policy" (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Personal Works - poetry (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Land Utilization Committee (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Long Term Finance (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - AIA - National Policy Task Force - 1st Edition (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - NYC/AIA - Financing Construction Committee 1968-1973 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - NYC Local Planning Boards (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Building Industry, Congress and the Money Question (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Medal of Honor, 1957 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Holden, McLaughlin and Associates Agreements, Analyses, Statements, etc. (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - West Point Address by A.C.H (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Copies, 1979 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Copies, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Copies, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - "Some Lessons from the Threat to Grand Central Station" (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - "Sonnets for my City" (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Bibliography by A.C.H. (Box 104, Folder 23)
- Series IX. Oversized photos and drawings
  Oversized photos and drawings from the Architectural League of New York Annual Exhibitions
  - Oversize Folder 3, Mapcase, Mathey Farm Group, Princeton, N.J.
    - Alterations to Barn for Dean Mathey, Aug. 24, 1926. Sheet #118, 136 (Folder 3)
    - Sehulman Place Garage, Oct. 5, 1926. Sheet #1, 142 (Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Masonry Details, Residence of Dean Mathey, Mar. 18, 1927 (Entrance and Garden Retaining Walls, and Serpentine Wall North of Barn) (Folder 3)
    - Residence of Dean Mathey, Fence Details, Sheet #1, Jun. 30, 1927, Sheet #2, Jul. 7, 1927. (Folder 3)
    - Stalls for Pretty Brook Farm, Jun. 21, 1928. Drawing #E (Folder 3)
    - One sheet for each F*S*D Sign Post, Aug. 24, 1928. (Folder 3)
    - Unlabelled view of Pretty Brook Farm, n.d. (Folder 3)
    - Perspective View of Pretty Brook Farm showing proposed additions to Farm Group, May 7, 1930. (Folder 3)
    - Proposed Additions to Farm group, May 7, 1930. (Folder 3)
    - Floor Plans for Gardner's Cottage, n.d. (Folder 3)
    - Proposed Squash Court Building, n.d. (Folder 3)
    - Elevation showing relationship between present barn and new building (dog run), Scheme "B," Apr. 28, 1930. (Folder 3)
    - Plan and Elevations of Shed, Scheme "A," Apr. 28, 1930. (Folder 3)
    - Plan of Dog Kennels, Wood Shed, Car & Tool Shed, Scheme "A1," Jun. 11, 1930. (Folder 3)
    - New Serpentine Wall, revised Jun. 10, 1930. Sheet #1, 224 (Folder 3)
    - Elevation of Gate and Plan of showing Gardener's Cottage and graveyard across the road, May 27, 1930. Drawing #2, 224 (Folder 3)
    - F*S*D Main Cornice - Dove Cote, n.d. Drawing #101, 224 (Folder 3)
    - F*S*D of Post Head, Graveyard Fence, Jun. 24, 1930. Drawing #102, 224 (Folder 3)
    - Gasoline Pump House, Dec. 19, 1930. Drawing #103, 224 (Folder 3)
    - Pop's Pond memorial plaque to Louis A. Mathey, Jul. 8, 1930. Drawing #104. Also, preliminary sketch of this, unnumbered & n.d., 224 (Folder 3)
    - Equestrians' sign, Jul. 8, 1930. Drawing #105, 224 (Folder 3)
    - Proposed Dam at Pop's Pond, Jun. 23, 1932, Holden McLaughlin & Associates, 670 Fifth Ave, New York. (Folder 3)
    - Front Entrance Gates for Dean Mathey, Esq., Jul. 12, 1932. (Folder 3)
  - Oversize Folder 4, Mapcase, Mathey, Dean, "The Bowery," Princeton, N.J.
    - Basement & Foundation Plan Mar. 25, 1930; revised Apr. 8, 1930, 1 (Folder 4)
    - First and Second Floor Plans and Details of the House, no date., 1A (Folder 4)
    - First Floor Plan, Feb. 25, 1930; revised Mar. 25, 1930., 2 (Folder 4)
    - Elevations, n.d., 2A (Folder 4)
    - Second Floor Plan, Mar. 25, 1930; revised Apr. 8, 1930., 3 (Folder 4)
    - Elevations, Feb. 25, 1930; revised Apr. 8, 1930 (North & South), 4 (Folder 4)
    - Elevations, Feb. 25, 1930; revised Apr. 8, 1930. (West & South), 5 (Folder 4)
    - Garage & Fence, Mar. 4, 1930., 6 (Folder 4)
    - Longitudinal Section through House, Feb. 25, 1930., 101 (Folder 4)
    - 3/4" & F*S*D of North Elevation, Mar. 26, 1930., 102A (Folder 4)
    - F*S*D of Main Cornice, North Elevation, showing details of Casements hinged at bottoms & relation to cornice, Mar. 26, 1930, 103 (Folder 4)
    - F*S*D Typical Window, Mar. 26, 1930, 104 (Folder 4)
    - Details of Dormers, Mar. 26, 1930, 105 (Folder 4)
    - Casement Window Frames in Masonry in "Study" Wing, Mar. 28, 1930, 106 (Folder 4)
    - Exterior Door Details, Mar. 31, 1930. (door at kitchen entry, at west side of dining room, east door from dining room to porch, south door from living room to porch), 107 (Folder 4)
    - 3/4" Sections & Elevation of Study Book Cases, May 9, 1930., 110 (Folder 4)
    - 3/4" & F*S*D of Hall Stair, May 10, 1930., 111 (Folder 4)
    - 3/4" Details of Fire Place in Bed Room #1, Apr. 29, 1930., 12 (Folder 4)
    - Drawing 6 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Drawing 7 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Drawing 8 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Drawing 9 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Drawing 10 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Drawing 16 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Drawings #13-15 of a study, a dining room and a flower room; two photographs of the exterior unlabelled building (Box 112)
- Series X. Maps
    - Final Damage Map, East River Drive, May 20, 1936 (Folder 1)
    - Maps of New York City, Queens (Folder 2)
    - Maps of Jacksonville, Florida, Manhattan, Quogue, Suffolk Co., Washington, D.C., and Brooklyn, showing topography, location of businesses, proposed and existing streets and parks, traffic and transportation, zoning, bridges, and aerial surveys. (Folder 3)
    - New York City housing maps and charts (Folder 4)
    - Mayor's Committee on City Planning material (Folder 5)
    - New York City charts and prints (Folder 6)
    - Tenement House Competition material (Folder 7)
    - New York State Board of Housing material (Folder 8)
    - Matt Fleming #2 (Folder 9)
    - Dwelling Law studies (Folder 10)
    - Survey Material I (Folder 11)
    - Survey Material II (Folder 12)
    - Maps II (Folder 13)
- Series XI. Rolled Plans
    - "A" Proposed Hotel Group 1927 charcoal on grey, "B" Proposed Hotel Group 1927 charcoal on grey, Lincoln Church Misc. details, 1 (Box 106)
    - Sanford Stoddard, Esq. Residence, 2 (Box 107)
    - Alterations and additions to "Hebron" for Miss Mabel Lindsay Gillespie, 3 (Box 108)
    - Sutton Hall Apartments, 4 (Box 109)
    - Henry B. Thompson Property William Green Estate, 5 (Box 110)
    - E.S. Schniewind residence, 6 (Box 106)
    - Sutton Hall Apartments, 7 (Box 111)